keralam.at 2014-06-16

# Privacy - Keralam.at

Last Updated on 01/11/2011 

This document sets forth the Online Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) for this Web site, http://www.keralam.at (the “Site”). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities or other web sites related to Keralam.at.

At http://www.keralam.at, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.keralam.at and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, http://www.keralam.at makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user?s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
http://www.keralam.at does use cookies. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.keralam.at.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to http://www.keralam.at and other sites on the Internet. 

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….   
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.keralam.at send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

http://www.keralam.at has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.keralam.at’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**  
All “personal information” (“personal information” is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Keralam.at reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. 

**Entities collecting personal information**  
The Site collects personal information such as email address, which we will store in our system. The Site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.

**Collection of personal information**  
As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. When you submit personal information to Keralam.at through this Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Keralam.at and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including, without limitation, the United States. 

Keralam.at collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. Keralam.at will NOT by any chance share any such personal information with any 3rd parties. We may use the personal information such as email for communications and newsletters.

Keralam.at may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Keralam.at may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

Also, please note that Keralam.at is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any other Web sites to which this Site may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.

Thanks for visiting Keralam.at!

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us: [Contact Us](mailto:keralam.at@gmail.com?subject=Copyright%20Video)
